# **ROBBIE PARR**

With over 7 years Python programming experience, React Native cross platform app development and 3D/VR Game development. Robbie is very motivated to learn new programming languages and frameworks, if he doesn't currently have a skill you want, he'll eagerly retrain and up-skill for you. In the past he has undertaken leadership roles and have encouraged team bonding, which improved team cohesion and performance at stress points in the project/group, making him an invaluable member of any team. After his studies finished, he created a community linking students and industry professionals in York, the Parr-ty Events, hosting several events, a BBQ event and a talk titled "Generative AI and the Future" being highlights. He is looking for his first graduate role.

### **Education**

University of York	BEng in Computer Science
Third year complete, results pending	2 <sup>nd</sup> Year Average 2:1 Classification

# **Key Technical Skills**

- Strong Programming in Python, Java and Haskell
- Other Programming in C & C++, C#, HTML, CSS, SCSS and JavaScript, R
- App development using React and React Native (With TailwindCSS Styling, Expo Deployment)
- Continuous Integration and Project Management in Git (GitHub)
- Code Architecture in UML
- Databases using Firebase, Sanity and SQLite (Using SQL and XML)
- App Modelling in Balsamiq Wireframes
- Games design using Unity, 3D modelling using Blender
- File storage and forms using Google Drive (Docs, Slides, Sheets, Sites)

## **Key Transferable skills**

Leadership

Responsible

Punctual

Organised

- Problem Solving

Efficient

- Hard-working

Trustworthy

Adaptable

- Mathematically Adept

- Scientifically Adept, Especially in Physics

Technologically Adept

- Diligence

- Dependable

Discretion

- Perseverance

- Resilience

Resourceful

- Reliable

## **Experience**

York Community Consulting	October 2022 - Current
Joined a technology focussed consultancy project as a Senior Consultant and upon completion of the project was promoted to a Software Developer in	<ul><li>Key takeaways</li><li>How to build a client facing</li></ul>
the wider YCC Technology team to continue developing the new YCC website. The website utilises React.JS/Next.Js, SCSS, JSX with a JavaScript	ReactJS/Next.Js web application Agile methodologies - Working in a team of Junior Software/Aspiring Full Stack Developers
backend and firebase data and API endpoints.	

# **ROBBIE PARR**

- Identifying the person in a team best
suited to complete a task to the highest
quality
- Github, as used in industry, including
rebasing

# **University of York, Baking Society**

March 2021 - March 2022, Three University Terms

President of the Baking Society; leading a fully new small interdisciplinary committee team, organising the society and the great events we put on, rejuvenating the buzz for in-person events after lockdowns, working with notes from previous, uncontactable, committee members. I proudly hosted a multitude of events, being the face of the society.

## Key takeaways

- What it's like to be in a leadership role
- Importance of good relationships with society members and members of small businesses.
- What it's like to have to go off incomplete information, with no point of contact to get clarifications
- What it's like for members of a team to leave/delay work for an extended period of time, how it impacts workload for the rest of a team
- How lenient/strict a leader can be when there are hard and soft deadlines
- Balancing University life while effectively running a organisation

# The Edinburgh Woollen Mill (Horsham Town Centre Branch)

February 2020 - September 2020,

# Worked as a Sales Assistant for the store. Helping with the selling of goods to customers. Ensuring an excellent customer experience.

# Key takeaways

- Customer facing interaction
- Money handling
- Understanding GUI systems and what features are required, understanding that the GUI must hide the "technical jargon" related to the processing of data and the inner workings of the system and connected devices

# **Shelton Development Services (Cranleigh)**

31 July – 4 August 2017

One-week work experience writing software using Python, Pygame, HTML and CSS to re-create a licence system for the company's software products.

# Key takeaway

- How to work effectively and efficiently as part of a
- How to communicate and ask for help in a team of Software Developers
- The branches of different avenues available for Software Developers